University Relations, Office of; Records ua760
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Photographs, 1967-1995; undated; 4.5 cubic feet
  - Geography, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Graduation, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Handicapped, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Kelly, Richard, Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Krivo, Frank G., 1960 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Lecture Center, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Library, 1978 July (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Library & Information Sciences, School of, 1980 November 5 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Music, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Nursing, School of, 1979 December 10 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Alumni House, Photographs, ca. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Alumni Photographs, 1936-1988 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Arch Downtown Campus, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Arch Outside Photographs, ca. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Architecture: Night and Winter, Photographs, ca. 1982 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Campus Construction Photography, 1966-1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Government Building Photography, 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Downtime Albany Photographs, ca.1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Downtown Campus Interior Photographs, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Uptown Campus Interior Photography, ca. 1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Architecture Detail Photographs, ca. 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Architecture Aerial Photography, ca. 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Administrator and Staff Photographs, ca. 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Photographs Fakes by Students Studying Abroad, ca. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Ambulance Five Quad, 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Annual Fund Photographs, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Anthropology Faculty Photographs, ca.1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Carillon Tower Photographs, ca. 1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Students in Class, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Performing Arts Center, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Pogue Frank, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Program Development and Evolution, Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Public Affairs, Graduate School of, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Reinfurt, Edward, Jr., 1972 June 8 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Rice, Bob, 1978 September 6 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Robin Day Care, Undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Social Welfare, School of, 1980 November 3 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Spellman, Seth, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Sports Women, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Staff, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Students, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Students, 1978 July (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Students, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Students in Class, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Students- Minority, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Students-Older, 1975-1982 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Students- Studying, 1979 December 10 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Wright, Nathan, Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Assorted Photographs and related documentation, ca. 1987-1997 (Box 3)
- Press Clippings, 1960-1970; 7 cubic ft.
  Files in this series have been maintained in their original order. The appear to have been primarily ordered chronologically by publication type.
  This series is made up of files of press clippings that the Office maintained. These files primarily document press coverage in campus publications such as the Tower Tribune and in local newspapers in the Greater Albany area, but coverage of the university in national publications such as the New York Times and Time appear as well.
  - Gould, Chancellor, 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chancellor Samuel B. Gould Press Clippings, 1966; 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - News Releases, 1960 October (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - News Releases, 1961 January (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - News Releases, 1961 January-1961 February (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - News Releases, 1961 March-1961 April (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - News Releases, 1961 May-1961 June (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - News Releases, 1961 July-1961 August (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - News Releases, 1961 September-1961 October (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - News Releases, 1961 December (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - News Releases, 1962 January (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - News Releases, 1962 February-1962 March (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - News Releases, 1962 May (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - News Releases, 1962 May (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - News Releases, 1962 July (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - News Releases, 1962 August-1962 September (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - News Releases, 1962 October-1962 December (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - News Releases, 1963 January-1963 February (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - News Releases, 1963 February-1963 March (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - News Releases, 1963 April-1963 May (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - News Releases, 1963 June-1963 July (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - News Releases, 1963 August-1963 September (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - News Releases, 1963 October-1963 December (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - News Releases Newsday Study on State Universities, 1964 January-1964 February (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - News Releases, 1964 February (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - News Releases, 1964 May-1964 June (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - News Releases, 1964 July-1964 September (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - News Releases, 1964 December (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - News Releases, 1965 January-1965 February (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - News Releases Knickerbocker, 1965 May (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - News Releases Time MAG. Universities The Giant Nobody Knows, 1965 June-1965 July (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - News Releases, 1971 November-1971 December (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - SUNYA News Press Release C.R.O. N. Lampman, 1969 January-1969 June (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - SUNYA News Press Release C.R.O. N. Lampman, 1969 July-1969 December (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - SUNYA News Press Release C.R.O. N. Lampman, 1970 January-1970 July (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - SUNYA News Press Release C.R.O. N. Lampman, 1970 August-1970 December (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - SUNYA News Press Release C.R.O. N. Lampman, 1971 January-1971 April (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - SUNYA News Press Release C.R.O. N. Lampman, 1971 May-1971 August (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - SUNYA News Press Release C.R.O. N. Lampman, 1971 September 2-1972 February 18 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Roundtable- Tuesday Breakfast, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Rhoads/Waterman 2 Albany Professors, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - University of the Air, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - CRO Log, 1970 May 5-1970 May 19 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - CRO Log, 1970 May 5-1970 May 19 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Office of Community Relations, 1981 January (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - SUNYA News Press Release C.R.O. N. Lampman, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - SUNYA News Press Release C.R.O. N. Lampman, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - News Clips, 1971 October-1973 October (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Log to Clippings, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - SUNYA News Clips, 1971 September-1974 May (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Letters to Editors, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Community Relations News Clippings Log Book, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Editorial Comment, 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Grants, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Selected Activities at SUNYA, 1969-1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Show-Cause Order ve Student Activity Fees, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Suny Master Plan And Rev, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Pending W/LTB, 1971 March-1971 April (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Tower Topic Tapes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Tower Tapes Radio Shows, 1969 February 9 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Academic Affairs, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Staff, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Senate, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Sports, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Official Notices, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Music, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - More Events, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Library, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Student Achievements, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Round The Campus, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Research, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Campus Exchange, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Art, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Course Offerings Faculty, Senate, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Conferences and Workships, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Campus Forums, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Opinion Columns, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Student Activities, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Suny Special Report on Energy, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - School of Criminal Justice Newsletter, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Mailing List For Tribune and ASP, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - University Open House, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - United Fund and Blood Drives, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Theater, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Suny and Board Of Regents, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Student Government, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Lectures and Special Programs, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Fiscal Affairs, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Fellowships and Grants, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Facilities, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Enrollment Figures, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Employee Relations, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Doctor of Arts Program, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Deaths, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Day Care Center, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Crime on Campus, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Student Association, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Notes, 1970-1973 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - SUNYA News Releases, 1970 September-1972 December (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - SUNYA News Releases, 1973 January-1973 April (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - SUNYA News Releases, 1973 May-1973 July (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - SUNYA News Releases, 1973 August-1973 December (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - SUNYA News Releases, 1974 January-1974 April (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - SUNYA News Releases, 1974 May-1974 July (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - SUNYA News Releases, 1974 August-1974 December (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - SUNYA News Releases, 1975 January-1975 June (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - SUNYA News Releases, 1975 July-1975 December (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - News, 1976 January-1976 December (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - University Centers Monthly Report, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1978 December-1979 February (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - SUNY-wide Press Clippings, 1979 March-1979 April (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - SUNY-wide Press Clippings, 1979 May-1979 June (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - SUNY-wide Press Clippings, 1979 June-1979 July (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - SUNY-wide Press Clippings, 1979 July-1979 August (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1972 December-1973 January (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1973 January-1973 February (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1973 February-1973 March (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1973 March-1973 April (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1973 April-1973 May (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1973 June-1973 July (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1973 August-1973 September (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1973 September-1973 October (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1973 October-1973 November (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1973 November-1973 December (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1973 December-1974 January (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1974 January-1974 February (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1974 February-1974 March (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1974 March-1974 April (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1974 April-1974 May (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1974 May-1974 June (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1974 June-1974 July (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1974 August-1974 September (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1974 September-1974 October (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1974 October-1974 November (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1974 November-1974 December (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1975 March -1975 April (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1976 December-1977 January (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1977 January-1977 February (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1977 February-1977 March (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1977 March-1977 April (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1977 April-1977 May (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1977 May-1977 June (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1977 June-1977 July (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1977 July-1977 August (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1977 August-1977 September (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1977 September-1977 October (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1977 October-1977 November (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - SUNY-wide Clippings, 1977 November-1977 December (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - University of The Arts, 1967 September 29 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Office of Public Relations, 1969 September 25 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Photography Releases, 1969 July 15 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - New York Office, 1971 March 2 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Communications Gp., 1971 November 19 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Vice Chancellor University Affairs, 1973 June 13 (Box 6, Folder 40)